Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Yannis!
Where is Edebali?
- I'm here because he's not, Osman.
- Stop beating around the bush!
- Answer my question!
- Edebali and his daughter are gone.
But I don't know where they are.
It won't take too long.
Don't forget that you're in my hands.
Killing me is the last thing you want
right now, Osman.
Devil!
Selcan Hatun.
What are you talking about? Selcan Hatun
is not even in Söğüt.
Your anger has left your sense in
the shade, Osman.
You're forgetting that we have hands
in every shadow.
What did you do to Selcan Hatun?
We will not decide on that. You will.
She is resting in the caravanserai,
unaware of everything.
- Welcome, Princess Sofia.
- Thank you.
What are you searching for, Selcan Hatun?
My dagger is here, but I can't find
Mother Hayme's reminiscence.
You go, continue your meal.
Yes, Princess?
To that table, send plenty of lamb
and fruits.
What gives, what are these?
Treats of Kulucahisar' Princess Sofia,
Selcan Hatun.
If I don't get out of here alive...
... one of my men is waiting outside
to fly the news to the caravanserai.
Are you ready to negotiate with
your devil, Osman?
What do you want?
In return of my life, Selcan Hatun's life.
You're lying!
You made this up to get out of my hands.
Thank you for accepting my treats.
It's not a holiday, nor a feast day.
What were the treats for, Hatun?
You're our guest here. Treats reflect
the host's respect and honour.
May I sit?
Dumb guests think they are the hosts.
This land is ours.
And about being a guest...
If you accept being a guest at my table,
go ahead and sit.
As you wish.
So you are that famous Selcan Hatun.
Even the wise Greek women of
Kulucahisar speak highly of you.
We look at the furnace, not the fire. If
our names are known, thanks to Mother Hayme.
I'm sure Mother Hayme's grandson...
... Osman Bey...
... will be very happy to see you.
Being related is divine for us, Princess.
But Osman is like a son to me.
I too, of course, missed him a lot.
Tell me.
Why do you have ties with Osman?
Osman Bey found my husband's
killers and punished them.
In our eyes, he is rather valuable.
Does this dagger look familiar, Osman?
Mother Hayme!
If you decline my offer, Selcan Hatun
will be needing this dagger very much.
She's like a mother to me.
If you hurt her...
... I'll take you even if you are in a well
full of snakes with my bare hands!
It's not over yet Osman.
Not only my life...
... I'll also give you Aybar's killers.
But then, of course, you'll be
silent during my execution.
- Selcan Hatun.
- Will be at the Tent safe and sound.
Now think carefully. You either go to the
castle and witness my execution...
Or return to the castle after taking
Aybars' revenge...
... and reunite with Selcan Hatun
you love as a mother.
This was a big trick, wasn't it?
Only I know you well.
You'll fake your death and disappear.
Now, this is the Osman Bey I know!
Both brave and intelligent.
Don't forget that I also show no mercy!
I... I'm a dead man Osman.
Where are Aybars' killers?
They are in the Dark Woods now.
And their leader...
... is Salvador.
Osman Bey!
Make haste! I don't even know...
... who will they hurt next.
This is not over, Yannis.
Your dark shadows, your bat-like face...
... will be drowned in the light of
my sword. Know that.
For our cause and Master Yannis.
Thanks to Osman Bey, we cut down a big
tumour of these lands.
As much of a clumsy hunter, Osman Bey
proved that he'll be a great Bey.
Why isn't Osman here?
You had to know that, Bamsı Bey.
Sofia isn't here either.
Gündüz Bey, something is wrong here.
Once Osman is here, we'll figure it out.
So, where is Osman, Dündar Bey?
Who can find sense in Osman's
business, Alişar Bey?
Next thing you know, he's here.
So, how do we know that this
corpse is that Yannis guy?
What if he isn't?
The only one who knows him other
than us is Osman.
And he didn't come to the execution.
Trust us, Bamsı Bey.
Even the corpse of someone like Yannis
will cause air pollution.
Take him away.
Alişar Bey. While you are here, we wish
to renew our old agreement.
After you, Alişar Bey.
Dündar Bey.
Gündüz, I don't feel at ease at all.
Your uncle is still running
after agreements.
And Osman isn't anywhere to be seen.
Don't you worry Bamsı Bey. My father Ertuğrul
Gazi laid the foundations of this agreement.
Ertuğrul Bey wanted to do this
agreement with Yorgopolos.
Not with these nasty ones. Gündüz Bey.
Not with these nasty ones.
Not with these. Where are you my Osman?
Where?
Congrats. You look like you
just heard some good news.
Thank God they took care of a matter that
would have costed countless lives.
You brought luck.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Pleasure to meet you.
If you allow me, I'd like to visit
you and Zöhre Hatun in your Tent.
Of course. Our doors are
always open to friendlies.
Aybüke, who are they?
I don't know, Selcan Hatun.
My lovely girl, where are you from?
Where do you come from, where do you go?
With Ahi Evran's follower Ahis, we are
the fellow sisters of Fatma Bacı, mother.
Who is the magnificent one?
My Father Sheikh Edebali.
If I were to go up to him, would
he be disturbed?
My father likes to pray and to receive
prayer. He will be pleased.
How gorgeous! You shine like the
moon, my sweet girl. Go on, light my way.
Don't mention it, Hatun.
If you allowed it, I would have shown you
my gratitudes, Efendi.
Manners aren't licking a mortals boots,
Hatun.
Manners are knowing where you stand
before the creator's glory.
Praise be! They don't call you the
Turkmen's father for nothing.
You entered the caravanserai with your
light, shook with your greatness...
... burnt with your wisdom.
Excuse me.
Would you mind telling us your name?
A martyr's mother, another martyr's wife,
Selcan Hatun from the Kayı.
Be careful just in case, brothers.
- Bora!
- Yes, my Bey.
You, Kanturalı and Boğaç, watch the
right side.
- Don't let anyone run away.
- As you wish, my Bey.
Come on.
Onur. With Demirbüken and Erkut, watch
the backside.
We'll attack on my mark.
From now on, we don't have covers for
our swords on our backs.
There is anger to scare the enemy, venom
to infect the cruel.
Either death or victory.
So, we'll burn Samsa' Tent.
We have arrived. From now on, only the
Angel of Death will wander in these lands.
You know that I lost my wife.
If you allow it, I would like to
marry your daughter Aygül.
Alişar Bey. Dündar Bey.
Sorry for making you wait. But the
agreement texts you were waiting for...
... are ready.
Now that the traitor Yannis is dead...
... nothing is stopping us from
sealing the agreement.
Will the agreement made while Osman isn't
here be valid? Dündar Bey.
On our ways, elders talk, the little
ones stay silent.
About the agreement. With my
brother's word...
... I have the seal.
- Dündar Bey.
- Princess Sofia.
One day I saw a really nice flower on the
shores of the Caspian.
I can still smell it.
Every time I see you, I remember
that flower.
And how poisonous it was.
Boran!
Where is Salvador?
Don't take the trouble, Osman Bey.
He'll find you.
That demon Yannis who was hurting our
relationship got what was coming to him.
Now it's time to make our friendship
everlasting.
But...
... you tried to make an agreement
without me.
And you had a run of bad luck.
In these lands, no flower can blossom...
... without Alişar Bey's permission.
Now let's honour my deceased
husband Yorgopolos all together.
We shall renew the agreement.
Let's finish what Dündar Bey started
together.
Also, different from the old one, the
perfume matter Dündar Bey wanted...
... has also been added to the agreement.
Are the articles we want in the agreement?
They are, Dündar Bey.
Alişar Bey, you look you you don't
trust us.
You're reading it very carefully.
A man with no care is a man with
no dignity, Kalonoz.
You'll pay for what you did to Aybars!
You will pay for it!
You can go. We'll inform you once
they talk.
- Boran.
- Yes, Bey.
My aunt Selcan is here. I need to go to
the Tent immediately.
Take this dog to our place.
- Make him talk until the morning.
- Don't you worry, my Bey.
He'll talk eventually.
Sergeant Samsa, you return to your Tent.
Wait for my word.
Welcome, Selcan Hatun!
Selcan Hatun.
That's all we needed among all
these troubles.
Good heavens! I saw Selcan Hatun with
my own eyes once again.
Ayşe.
My Aunt. Welcome.
My sweet girl.
- Welcome, Aunt Selcan.
- My Aygül.
- Welcome Selcan Hatun.
- Thank you.
Welcome, Selcan Hatun.
What happened, Zöhre?
Your face turned pale.
We're surprised, Hatun.
It's nice to have you back.
Where is my dark-eyed Osman?
I've heard. Tell me. You put my
Osman in cages.
Looks like trees started talking.
All beings start talking before
Selcan Hatun. Don't you know it, Zöhre?
Stop beating around the bush and tell me.
Where is my Osman?
Dündar Bey said the cage would tame him
but...
... he punished himself.
He tamed himself.
Now, only Allah knows where he is.
We couldn't keep up with him when he
was a little kid.
I'm sure he knows what he's doing.
Aygül. Bring me some ayran.
My heart is all dry.
Right away, aunt Selcan.
Go ahead.
Go ahead, Selcan Hatun.
You established your Tent on the
shadow of Ertuğrul Bey's Tent.
But don't you know, no grass grows on
his Tent's shadow.
Even though it's not a Tent worthy of
Dündar Bey, we keep on living, thankfully.
I hope Allah blesses you and your
loved ones with long lives.
- Amen.
Winter is near.
People don't migrate in these seasons.
Is it good or bad, Selcan Hatun?
Only Allah knows that, Zöhre.
What gives, are you afraid we'll
disturb you?
Not at all. I worry about you.
I hope nothing is wrong.
I'm tired, Zöhre. My Tent is also tired.
After my Gündoğdu passed away,
I can't stay there.
I have arrived. My Tent will be on the
road eventually.
Inshallah.
Who are these strangers?
Not strangers, Bamsı Bey. They are snakes.
Snakes.
On me...
You have something on me that's
tiring my shoulders, Bamsı Bey.
These little devils...
... are my brother Aybars' killers.
They also have a leader.
I'll also bring him to you.
That old guy wasn't Yannis. Was he?
He's the head of the snake.
I caught him from the tail.
We'll crush his head eventually.
Don't you worry.
Now...
Taking revenge is your job, not
mine, Bamsı Bey.
Their blood can flow like
the Alaca River...
... that still wouldn't ease my pain.
My Osman. May you live long!
May you live long.
I was wrong about you, Osman Bey.
I thought you had forgotten about Aybars.
In our friendship, forgetting is
not a thing, Burçin Hatun.
Bamsı Bey.
People!
Brothers!
Sisters! Friends!
Today is the day
the fire inside me cools down!
Today is the day I take my martyr
son Aybars' revenge!
These snakes thought...
... we would forget about our pain
and not go after it!
The snakes thought
we don't seek revenge!
But...
... my dear Osman, with his claws
like an eagle...
... took them and brought them to me!
Now it's my turn to separate their
poisonous heads from their tails.
In the name of Allah!
Allahu Akbar!
(Allah is the Greatest)
Long live Osman Bey! Long live Bamsı Bey.
www.kurulusosman.online
This is the day we cut the heads of
all the snakes...
... trying to slither into
the Turks heart!
It's time to, with our faith...
... march towards Kızıl Elma!
My dark-eyed, valiant Osman!
- Welcome, aunt.
- Thank you.
When I saw you, I saw the welcome
ones, pleased ones, son.
Come, we shall go to my father's Tent.
He found the governors killer. He found
Aybars' killers and brought them to the Tent.
Osman is like a gurgling waterfall.
Either we stand in his way to stop him...
... or he will flood us all.
His father's lion!
Kayı's prosperity, my Osman.
Osman, don't let your eyelashes
cover your eyes.
Tell me what bothers you.
You are alive and well, aunt.
This takes my anxiety away.
Thank Allah.
Have a seat.
Oh, my Osman. Your dreams will come true.
Kayı Tents are going to unite.
Someday, all the Oghuz tents will be
strong and united.
In sha Allah, my lion.
In sha Allah.
I heard that you went to the caravanserai.
(A roadside hotel for travellers in old times.)
Yes, I did.
I hope nothing's wrong.
Osman.
Where did you find this dagger?
Was there anyone who drew your attention
in the caravanserai?
Yes.
Princess of Kulucahisar came to me.
- Sofia.
But, what does Sofia have to do with
this dagger, son?
They want me to forgive someone's life
in return of your life, aunt.
You don't say!
Is it Sofia?
Yannis.
Who is Yannis?
- We will talk about it in the evening, aunt.
- My Osman...
When I was at the caravanserai,
I met Sheikh Edebalı.
Are you serious, aunt?
Your face is shining like the moon,
my lion. What happened?
You gave me very important news.
What about his daughter?
Was his daughter with him?
- Do you mean Bala Hatun?
- Yes.
Of course.
I met her too.
Where are you going?
I have to go to the caravanserai
immediately, aunt.
We have a lot of things to talk about
this evening.
I have never thought that my death would
amuse them that much.
Edebali.
- He'll believe you are dead, sir.
- So, he'll make his moves more comfortably.
If it was so easy, I would have already
died until now.
Prince Salvador!
Osman is trapped, sir.
Now it's the big wolf's turn.
I thought you would be sorry for your
warriors, Prince Salvador!
Only digressing from my ideas
can upset me, Commander.
- Do we have a destination, sir?
- Yes, of course.
Our destination is the straight path.
- Of course, sir.
My dear friends.
To remain a Muslim is more important
than being born a Muslim.
They can torture us, they can banish
us from our land.
Even a scholar can't teach
an ignorant person.
We will keep on going.
We are not going to change our
destination.
Remember this, friends.
Whoever obeys abasement will be awarded
with dignity and greatness.
- Eyvallah (thank you) sir.
Sir, they say Yannis has been killed.
A mouse sees a piece of bread.
The mouse looks at both where he stands
and where the bread is.
And he says "there's something wrong."
"The bread is big.
Also, the distance is too short."
What do you suspect, sir?
Yannis is a big bait.
Besides, it is weird that he is gone
easily.
In my opinion, a girl like Sofia never
accepts his father's execution.
- Their intention is clear.
- Only you know the place of the treasure.
- They know this, don't they?
- Yes.
They do.
That's why they are going to trap Osman.
They are going to aim to confuse him,
to change his mind.
Did Osman go to the execution ceremony?
He didn't, sir.
So, the devil started to confuse him.
When he talks with Selcan Hatun,
he will come to you, sir.
He will want to see you.
- Peace be with you.
Can you notify Edebali that I want to see
him, Dervish?
Eyvallah (okay).
Osman Bey.
Bala Hatun.
Thank Allah, I've found you.
I was worried because you left the tent
suddenly.
Is your father angry with me?
He sensed it, Osman Bey.
I know, it was my bad.
I disappointed him.
I came here to seek forgiveness.
My father doesn't turn away anyone who
comes to him, Osman Bey.
Also, he is upset about what you did.
He wants to guide you.
He is our light.
I didn't want to upset him.
Do you know why you upset my father?
I know, Bala Hatun.
I tried to be the justice instead of
fighting for justice.
That's right.
He'll be happy to see you.
In sha Allah.
In sha Allah, Bala Hatun.
I want to see him and recieve his prayers.
Also, I have something to tell him.
Then, I'll tell you too.
While waiting for my father,
have a seat, Osman Bey.
- We saw your aunt Selcan.
- I know.
I've found you thanks to her.
I was scared that I couldn't see you
again, Bala Hatun.
I'll send my Selcan aunt to your father,
to ask for our marriage.
What's wrong?
- Peace be with you.
- Peace be with you, Akça Dervish.
- Welcome, Osman Bey.
- Thank you.
I want to see Edebali.
He is not available, Osman Bey.
- Does he know that it is important?
- Yes.
- I'll see him myself.
- Osman Bey!
Be patient.
Patience solves every problem.
www.kurulusosman.online
Your father turned me away, Bala Hatun.
Now, are you angry with my father because
he turned you away?
Or do you angry with yourself, who raised
his hand to an unreachable position?
I did this to myself.
A little problem may bother you.
But, even big problems have their
solutions.
I can't surrender, Bala Hatun.
Then, you need to be patient.
- Do you like our pot of secrets, Akça?
It leaks water, sir.
Then, we need to flame it.
My father knows something for sure,
Osman Bey
I know, being patient is hard.
I can wait until my last breath.
As long as I know that you can wait too.
I can be your friend in my father's way.
I can wait until my last breath for this
cause.
However, know that this will be hard.
Be my hope if I go hopeless.
I just need to know that you will be mine.
Do not doubt.
I can be yours until the end of my life.
I will be back, Bala Hatun.
You were going to say something to me.
- Aygül Hatun.
- What happened to her?
She came to me in the tent.
She said we troubled both you and
the tent.
She warned me.
You don't need to go crazy, Osman Bey.
She is from your own blood.
It is not her business.
It's not about you or me, Osman Bey.
What is it about, then?
Aygül Hatun likes you.
I know that my heart belongs to you,
Bala Hatun.
Leave Aygül to me.
However, I didn't know I upset Edebali
so much that he didn't want to see me.
I will wait patiently.
I am leaving, Bala Hatun.
Your Efendi isn't available, Osman Bey.
Be patient. Patience is the door to the
ultimate union, you know.
Come here. Sit.
Come.
Your father has something
to talk to you, daughter.
Listen carefully.
My daughter...
in our traditions...
having a daughter is precious.
Because she is a guest who leaves
when the time comes.
And your time has come, daughter.
I want you to settle in a smooth place...
... not in a brow.
I want you to marry a man
who knows your worth.
Today...
I was with Alişar Bey in Kulucahisar.
He lost his wife, you know.
He wants you as his wife.
He asked me about it...
... and I'm asking you, daughter. Do you
have consent?
Your father is asking you.
Whatever you like, father.
Daughter...
... you look so confused.
Be on your own for a while.
Think properly.
Okay.
Girls can't think straight, Dündar Bey.
You can't leave her alone with such
an important decision.
Consent is very important!
My daughter isn't for sale in New Bazaar!
Let her decide on her own.
Look at the fires of the candles, Kalanoz.
They're so timid, they're shaking.
They'll go out if I blow.
Our dreams will come true, darling.
We'll defeat Turks together.
Master Yannis will show us the way.
We'll walk together in that way.
As long as you look at me like this...
... as long as there's a fire of love
in our hearts...
... we can do everything.
Why is she here?
They have migrated. They'll
settle in the tent.
50 tents equals 500 people, Hatun.
We can't afford anything these days.
And now here they are.
She asked about Osman.
There's no need to mention Selcan Hatun.
Keep your eyes on her.
Welcome, aunt.
Thanks, Dündar Bey.
Come. It's all for you.
Thank you.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful)
Brother fought with his brother...
... and the idiot believed it.
Batur...
Osman...
Tell me. Is this true?
Is there a sibling fight in our tent?
No, aunt.
You are right.
But, Osman adjudicated without my
permission.
My Batur.
My Valiant.
Let's ask Osman.
Aunt, let's drop this subject.
Let's keep it cool.
My Gündüz.
My sunlight.
We can only solve this problem by
going after it.
Not by escaping it.
This case is so new, Selcan Hatun.
If we push it, it'll be worse.
You mustn't push it.
We have been taught by Mother Hayma,
Söhre Hatun.
I've lived through three Bey's reign.
My intention is not to push.
I want to find a solution.
Osman, tell me.
Is Batur right?
He hit me when I least expected it.
I didn't expect this from Osman.
My Osman.
Is what Batur says right?
Little Osman.
Young Osman.
Patience is the key.
Know this very well.
Yes, aunt.
He is not flawless.
But, I acted impulsively.
Osman..
My dark-eyed valiant.
Strangers spoil the brotherhood.
I left a son and my valiant Gündoğdu
behind.
I have no one else to trust but you.
If you divide, how can I stand?
This is my grandfather Korkut's
bequest.
The ignoble tries to disunite brothers,
while the decent tries to unite.
Come on, hug each other.
Let this lament end.
Let's turn the bad smell in the air into
a sweet smell.
Give me your blessings.
I do.
Hay Masha Allah (may Allah protect it.)
Aunt, you brought your compassion.
Bless you.
Your tent needs a mother.
A mother's compassion.
Daughter.
I see you are rather silent.
Come here.
I hope nothing is wrong, in sha Allah.
I am fine, father.
I am fine, but...
... something bothers me.
Tell me what bothers my sunshine.
Our situation, father.
We face injustice everywhere we go.
They set traps for us.
How can we achieve the comfort?
This question bothers me.
Your decedent Mother Ulduz Hatun
was just like you.
When something bothered her, she would
sit in a corner and think all day long.
My daughter, my Bala.
Your heart is bothered, not you.
A person is full of blood.
But his heart manages him.
Body is a nacre, heart is a pearl.
Skin is an envelope,
heart is a letter.
The heart is the capital of a huge
country, daughter.
It is like a herbalist, who includes
all the cures.
If you find the justice in your heart,
you will arrive at the land of goodness.
If you find wisdom in your heart,
you'll arrive at the land of philosophy.
If you find compassion in your heart,
you'll arrive at the land of mercy.
If you find love in your heart, you'll
arrive at the land of servitude.
As our prophet ordered...
If our heart is strong,
all of our works will be successful.
However, this shouldn't bother you.
Since when have you been bothering
yourself for us, for yourself, Bala Hatun?
If you think of yourself, you'll have
a lot of troubles.
A person always have problems.
A person is made of his problems.
In the Islam world, our trouble is so
small...
when compared to the oppresseds' troubles.
If you're bothered with all the
humanity's troubles someday...
that day will be our salvation Inshaallah.
May Allah...
... make clear all of our hearts.
May Allah make our trouble big.
So that the devil can't
pervade our heart.
So that our heart will always be clean.
Amin.
Don't ever talk!
Don't!
I'll start with your fingers...
Then I'll cut your eyelids!
Stop, brother. Stop.
Let me go.
- Stop, brother.
- Let me go!
Okay, okay! Okay! I'll tell you!
Tell us! Tell us so you can die easily.
I'll tell everything!
But don't make him touch me.
Salvador will raid Samsa's tent tomorrow.
He'll meet his men in Caravanserai.
Tell me...
How will we recognize him?
There's a big sign behind his head.
Wait here, brother.
I'll inform our Bey.
Come on!
I still remember the day
My Ertuğrul Bey...
... brought your late mother to the tent.
They survived so many hardships.
So many bad things happened to...
... your mother and father just because
she came to the tent.
May Allah rest my Halime.
She stood up to everyone and everything.
Even to me.
She said that you'd follow your father.
She was right.
You'll deal with the men of the
devil named Yannis.
Don't worry, aunt.
I'll deal with that devil.
I know.
Tell me...
... what do you wish?
I love Bala Hatun, aunt.
I can tell from your eyes, son.
Even when you say her
name, your eyes glow.
Tell me...
... what do you want?
I want you to go to Edebalı's place
tomorrow.
My Osman...
With Allah's order...
I want you to ask for (marriage)
Bala Hatun, aunt.
Thank Allah, we've seen these days.
Why do you send me when
there's your father?
He has a long way to go, aunt.
I don't know when he'll return.
And...
I'm out of patience.
We'll hold the wedding
when my father comes.
And...
I broke Edebalı's heart.
I did some bad things.
He warned me.
But...
... it was too late, aunt.
Your uncle...
Should I ask for Bala Hatun
when there's your uncle?
My uncle...
... is half my father, aunt.
But...
... you're my mother.
I'd die for you.
I don't need Dündar Bey...
when my mother is here.
Don't worry...
I'll visit that holy man Edebalı tomorrow.
Thanks, aunt.
And there's one more problem, aunt.
Tell me.
Aygül.
Your father closed the door
to his guest, Bala Hatun.
Love and compassion is like a
river inside a person.
If it flows strong, the evil
can't hold it.
Osman Bey...
... babbles like a river.
His love and compassion are
strong, thank Allah.
But...
... he's so cruel.
And overhasty.
And wrathful.
He said he would be with you...
... until his last breath.
Don't you believe him?
I do, but...
Then what?
My father left Osman in a hard position.
I am scared of the fact that...
... he may struggle too much.
Osman Bey.
Be patient.
Patience solves every problem.
Osman...
Osman, who goes high suddenly, then
goes low immediately...
Little Osman.
We tell you to be fair...
We tell you to be merciful...
We tell you to stand against cruelty...
And may people see the state in you...
But, look at what you have done.
Little Osman.
Young Osman.
Patience is the key.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
Boran.
What are you doing here?
- Where is Kanturalı?
- I left him, my Bey.
Why?
Why are you here?
Hoan spoke, my Bey.
Salvador will raid Samsa Bey's tent.
- We can't leave you alone.
- Damn faithless'!
They will raid Sergeant Samsa, ha?
I will rip their hearts off and let the
dogs eat them!
My Alps, let's go to Sergeant Samsa's
tent.
We will make them pay!
Eyvallah, (Okay) my Bey.
As years pass...
... Kayı tent has changed, Aybüke.
It has gotten old, and it has gotten
bigger.
And it has gotten more troubles.
We are in the middle of those troubles,
my Hanım (lady).
We came up to a complicated time.
What does bother you?
Zöhre Hatun.
I guess she is not so happy to see us.
Why would she be happy?
She set a brother against another.
They left my Osman alone.
She knows that I love him as my son.
She is anxious because I am here now.
Zöhre Hatun bears a grudge.
I hope she doesn't hurt you.
What Zöhre Hatun knows is only Dündar
Bey's bed.
I experienced three ages, and three huge
migration.
Look at the color of this hair.
She only makes herself listened to the
young ones.
She cannot command me.
Archers!
Shoot me.
You can be martyred at any time.
I don't accept any faults!
Know that very well!
We've raided infidel cities for a war.
The regulation has changed!
From now on, we will protect our land,
our honor, our tent!
The Beys in the Turkish tents act
carelessly!
You will fight, you will kill
the infidel!
Don't come to me without killing ten
infidels before being martyred!
I will chase you in the next world!
- Understood?
- Yes, my Bey!
Everyone knows what to do!
The genie is out of the bottle!
We will end this today!
We have just a single
arrow in the quiver!
This is our only chance!
If we fail...
We may not sleep at nights from now on.
Do you understand me?
Yes, Selcan Hatun?
Is there something important?
I came to talk about Aygül Hatun.
I will cut it short.
Do you not cut it short normally?
No.
What happened to my daughter?
I know Aygül likes Osman.
Who told you that?
I see it in your eyes. So it's true.
Tell me what do you want to say.
Osman loves another Hatun, Zöhre.
Both I and my daughter know that Osman
likes Edebalı's daughter.
What does this have to do with me or
my daughter?
If so, why did Aygül threaten Bala Hatun?
She says "we don't want you here, you
draw our tent into trouble."
My daughter is right.
But, not because she likes Osman.
Because she knows both that Hatun
and her father will trouble our tent.
Also, Aygül likes Alişer Bey.
Alişer Bey asked for my daughter's hand
from Dündar Bey, by the grace of Allah.
This conversation is over.
I am happy about this.
May Allah make them happy, in sha Allah.
Amin.
Obviously, there are things to do in
this tent, Zöhre.
I'll go back to my things.
I've heard you were
looking for me, Osman Bey.
You are looking for the killer
of Aybars, who I slaughtered.
Well then, here I am.
Salvador.
Come, let us solve this as men do.
When did you come and
confront me as a man, Salvador?
Are you brave with your
sword, or your tongue?
You took so many of my men's lifes for just one of
your Alps, did you really think I would forget that?
Now you are in my hands.
Our fire of vengeance doesn't extinguish
until the soil has enough blood.
I won't kill you until you have
enough of your own casualties!
- Allah is Great!
- Allah is one!
Attack!
Alps.
Erkut!
Erkut! Brother!
Drop your sword if you don't
want your Alps to die, Osman!
I won't tell you again!
My Bey. Don't!
Erkut! Erkut!
You called me, mother.
Come, daughter, sit.
I need to talk to you.
I wanted to talk to
you about Alişar Bey.
Your father won't give you to him
without your consent, you know that too.
But you have to marry Alişar Bey, Aygül.
The future of your father, us, our Tent,
and even your brother depends on it.
What are you saying,
mother? What future?
- Your father's future of Beyhood, daughter.
- Mother, do you hear your words?
Look, daughter.
I am a healer,
Ertuğrul Bey is sick for days.
He's been hiding this from everyone,
I knew it too but I stayed silent.
When the time comes, your father's
chance for Beyhood will be clear.
What does it have to do with me, mother?
Don't you know how vindictive Osman is?
After all that happened, Osman will neither
forgive your father nor your brother.
If your father doesn't become Bey,
eventually, Osman will be.
No one could prevent that from happening.
Except for Alişar Bey.
Did you understand me?
I've arranged a feast of
blood for you, Osman.
Even death won't save you from me!
No, no!
- Where is Edebali?
- Osman Bey, don't you tell a thing to this infidel!
- Demirbüken!
- I would give my life for you.
- This is such an emotional scene.
- I bear witness that there is no god but Allah...
- No!
... and I bear witness that Muhammad
is His servant and messenger.
No!
At the sunrise, and the sunset...
... every moment you don't tell me where
Edebali is, I will cut one of your Alps' throats.
We are leaving!
Demirbüken, Demirbüken!
Erkut!
Water, water!
Shut your mouth!
I've told you everything you wanted!
A little bit water.
If something happens to Samsa Bey...
... I will flay your skin!
Water.
Are these carpets worth putting in the
stalls of the skillful women of Kayı?
Since when the daughters of
Hayme Hatun, Halime Hatun...
...have left weaving and
started working with rags?
We would sit on the bench at
sunrise, and leave with the sunset.
We would treat our fingers
with balsam pear...
... to stop the pain.
Go and continue your work.
Tell me, Zöhre Hatun, have I spoken too much?
Do you think these carpets are worthy of Kayı Tent?
You are right, but nothing
is the same as before.
We collect the plants from Söğüt, they don't
give their colors fully even if we boil them for days.
These are all just excuses
for your misery.
I know.
You are blinded by the
profits you can make.
Hatuns, my sisters!
Is it too hard to find rare
plants and bring them?
Is it too hard to weave the best carpet?
From now on, we can continue
the way that Mother Hayme left.
I know that the girls of
Kayı Tent is very skillful.
Now, let them see what can Kayı
Tent's girls do with their talents.
I know, we will weave such carpets here that
even you won't look back to what you worked on before.
We meet again, Selcan Hatun.
Welcome, Dündar Bey is in his tent, come.
Zöhre Hatun, we are here
to honor the peace.
We came here as friends.
And you wanted to see the
carpets, princess, come.
Let's see, how strong is this Osman
Bey that people don't stop talking about.
Free me, and we shall see that together.
This dog doesn't
have the heart, my Bey.
These idiots can only kidnap Hatuns
from the marketplace for gold.
Then they walk the
lands as brave warriors.
Enough of this trash talk!
Tell us your price and we will buy you...
... like the dog you are!
My Bey!
Osman Bey!
You are a dog!
Your turn will come too!
Don't worry.
Where is Edebali?
He's in the place
that you will die!
My Bey!
Allah is Great!
Osman Bey!
Where is Edebali?
He fell asleep.
Father?
Are you alright, Inshallah?
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Osman.
What happened to Osman, father?
Send word to dervishes, daughter.
Tell them to check the forest carefully.
That horse...
What are you up to again, Osman?
Who are you?
I have an important
offer for you, Dündar Bey.
Tell me about it.
Alişar Bey is ambitious.
But we can do greater things together.
You are sailing too
close to the wind, Kalonoz.
Don't you know that you
can't even walk in these lands...
... without Alişar Bey's notice?
Alişar Bey is nothing without us!
I know that very well, Dündar Bey.
Just get to the point, Kalonoz.
Marketplaces are not
just in Söğüt or Eskihisar.
There are also markeplaces in our
lands, waiting to be alive again.
Those marketplaces are weak and poor.
But together, we can enhance
both our income and our power...
... by reviving the marketplaces
in the Byzantine.
What do you say?
Your carpets, fabrics...
... are amongst the most sold
goods in Constantinople.
It seems people of Constantinople know
a good carpet when they see one.
What is your wish, Princess?
Increase your carpets, produce more goods.
We want to directly take them
and sell them in Constantinople.
More carpets mean more
Hatuns, more benches.
We are ready to provide whatever you need.
We will do this together with
Selcan Hatun, right, Hatun?
If you are going to live
here, gold is important.
If it was just gold and coins, these
wouldn't be trapped in their stone castles.
I will consider it anyway.
Ya Allah, Ya Allah!
Brother!
He's alive, he's alive!
They have Osman Bey!
Go and tell the Tent!
Go and inform our sir, I will
carry the wounded to the Tent!
Okay, brother. Okay.
Ya Allah!
You see, your Alps care about you.
Let's see which one
of them you care more.
Is that this restless one?
Coward!
You will pay for what you did!
Demon!
You are a demon!
You will die!
Or is that this barbarian?
He even has battle wounds on his face.
I am sorry you will die in a pitiful way,
but Osman will decide when you will die.
Huh, Osman?
Tell me...
which one?
What I'm saying is, friends,
Yusuf's dungeon was dark.
What turned that dark dungeon
to a beautiful garden was Yusuf's faith.
It wasn't the well...
... or Egypt, or the dungeon
that made Yusuf holy.
One could need light to
escape from the well...
... or a decree to
get out of the dungeon...
... or wisdom to be a Sultan to Egypt.
But faith is what one needs to
have in order to be like Yusuf.
Amenna (We believed).
Faith turns the future to reality...
... far to close, and
defeated to victorious.
May Allah makes us the ones
that are free in any way.
Amin.
Attack on the New Bazaar was bad
for the reputation of the region.
But it seems that there won't be anyone
who will be there after it's reestablished but us.
Edebali.
There is Edebali, Dündar Bey.
Âhi is what people think when
you talk about craft, trade.
Âhi means trouble, Bamsı Bey,
it means big trouble for everyone.
Neither I or Alişar Bey
can give him a place there.
We have to take advantage of the
absence of the Âhis and other merchants.
My nephew, you stay strong.
People still didn't forget about it, uncle,
the blood is still fresh in the Bazaar.
It wouldn't suit us to use the
attack for something like this.
This is not using, my nephew.
And do you think I am not in pain?
Are these people going
to eat sorrow, drink tears?
We need to reestablish the Bazaar
quickly and let people trade there.
And everyone saw that the
marketplace that is not protected by...
... my Kayı Alps, is
suitable for an attack.
This will also...
... increase our reputation in the region.
Does Sofia agree with
this decision, Dündar Bey?
Sofia made a promise to me
with his Commander Kalonoz.
She will continue the way her
deceased husband Yorgopolos left.
If only you cared about Sheyh
Edebali, coming to our lands...
... as much as you care about
an alliance with the enemy!
Don't forget that Mongols
took Gündoğdu Bey and his son.
Edebali brought trouble wherever he went.
We don't want any
more blood to be spilled.
You shouldn't have bothered,
Zöhre Hatun, you can't escape your fate.
I hope nothing's wrong.
May I come in, Dündar Bey?
- Abdurrahman!
- Father!
Brother?
Come inside, Abdurrahman Ghazi!
Peace be with you.
Where is my brother, Abdurrahman Ghazi?
Don't be silent, Abdurrahman Gazi.
What is my father's condition?
Abdurrahman Gazi.
We went to many healers from Konya...
... to Kayseri with my Ertuğrul Bey.
Doctors from Gevher
Sultan Infirmary said that...
... "the illness has
spread to his lungs...
... he needs to be treated,
he should stay here for a while."
- His remedy will be Allah, inshallah.
- Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Father.
- Sir, may I?
- Speak, Dervish Pehlivan.
Osman Bey and his Alps
were ambushed in the forest.
They were taken.
Who did this?
We don't know, sir.
Prepare my weapon.
Friends...
... this is not the day
to be a Pîr, but a soldier.
We won't leave Osman alone.
We won't stand still either, father.
Ertuğrul Bey thinks about his
Tent, even in his condition.
He's afraid that Tent's
business could be hindered.
This is the will of Ertuğrul Bey,
son of Süleyman Şah.
He said "my Brother Dündar...
..." will be my deputy.".
He said "my sons should
obey...
... their uncle, and my Beys
should obey their Ağa...
... so that everything would be easier."
I congratulate your Beyhood, Dündar Bey.
May your Beyhood be magnificent,
may your sword be sharp, My Bey.
I sharpened my sword...
... with your eyes, thank you, Hatun.
Thank you.
- I congratulate you, father.
- Thank you, daughter.
- May Allah help you on your way, my Bey.
May your Beyhood be great, father.
Thank you, my son.
May Allah help you on your way, uncle.
My father's will.
I will obey you, and make your job easier.
My brother will come to this Tent...
... on his horse, safe and sound.
Don't be upset about it.
If it's...
... the order of...
... our Ertuğrul Bey...
... then we will obey, Dündar Bey.
Congratulations, Dündar Bey.
My brother...
May I come in, my Bey?
Come, Yaman.
My Bey, they brought Erkut
Alp, he is heavily wounded.
Demirbüken has been martyred.
What are you saying, what are you saying?
Where is my Osman, where are the others?
They are all captives.
Kill me, kill me!
You infidel!
Kill me! Kill me!
If you don't kill me now...
... I will rip your lungs out and
feed them to the dogs!
If you want it that much-
Stop, Salvador!
Leave him.
Let us enjoy their deaths.
Princess Sofia.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com